Guide to the John T. Davis Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2019-046
  - Willis, Kelly – 5 photographs, 6 slides; 1993 and 1999 interview notes; 1993 interview notes with Tony Brown; 11 x 17 Guy Juke poster (2 folders) (Box 2975, Folder 8-9)
  - Wilson, Eddie (club owner; Threadgills) (Box 2975, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Kim – 1 photograph (Box 2975, Folder 11)
  - Wittliff, Bill (writer, photographer) (Box 2975, Folder 12)
  - Womack, Lee Ann – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1997, 2001 (Box 2975, Folder 13)
  - Young, Faron – 1 photograph (Box 2975, Folder 14)
  - Zoe, Natalie – 1 photograph of the Alliance including Malford Milligan; handwritten letter (Box 2975, Folder 15)
  - Zydeco, General – 4 photographs: C.J. Chenier/Los Lobos; Lil' Brian; Zachary Richard; Jo-el Sonier (Box 2975, Folder 16)
  - ZZ Top – 1 photograph; Texas H.R. 48, 1986, "ZZ Top Day" in Texas (Box 2975, Folder 17)
  - Additional interview notes (Box 2975, Folder 18)
    Scope and Contents
    Asleep at the Wheel, May 2018; Kenny Rogers, February 26, 2017; Jeff McCord, KUTX-FM music director, January 22, 2014; Amos Traystman, Nightowls guitarist, January 24, 2014; Jill and Heidi, January 22, 2014; Ryan Harkrider, Nightowl for Austin Monthly, January 21, 2014; James White, June 10, 2013; Old Settlers list, 1999-2011
  - Additional promotional photographs (folder 1 of 4) (Box 2975, Folder 19)
    Karen Brooks – 3 photographs (2 with Randy Sharp); Sarah Elizabeth Campbell – 3 photographs; Mary Chapin Carpenter – 6 photographs; Johnny Cash – 6 photographs (1 with the Highwaymen); Bobby Charles; The Chieftains; Albert Collins
  - Additional promotional photographs (folder 2 of 4) (Box 2975, Folder 20)
    Ronnie Dawson; Bo Diddley; The Dirty Dozen Brass Band; Dr. John – 2 photographs; Betty Elders; Ramblin' Jack Elliott; Evangeline; Chris Gaffney; High Noon – 2 photographs; Etta James – 3 photographs; George Jones – 6 photographs; Norah Jones – 2 photographs
  - Additional promotional photographs (folder 3 of 4) (Box 2975, Folder 21)
    Alison Krauss – 4 photographs and 1 slide; Shelly Lares – 2 photographs; Los Lobos – 5 photographs; Shelby Lynne; Kathy Mattea – 2 photographs; The Mavericks – 5 photographs
  - Additional promotional photographs (folder 4 of 4) (Box 2975, Folder 22)
    Katy Mofatt – 3 photographs (1 signed); Bill Monroe; Patsy Montana – 2 photographs; Allison Moorer – 2 photographs; Maura O'Connell; Roy Orbison, Buck Owens; Dolly Parton – 2 photographs; George Porter, Jr. – 2 photographs; Bonnie Raitt; Traveling Wilburys
  - Weekender newspaper, May 12, 1978 (Box 2975, Folder 23)
  - 1986/1987 Austin Music Awards "Winner" T-shirt (Box 2975, Folder 24)